The End
Stop right there!
Unless you want to die, move!
All three of you, get away from the water!
Don't go trying to do anything funny.
The enemy here is one of you!
You!
Enemy.
Don't act like you're innocent.
I'm talking about the one that killed
that guard and tried to drown us.
Now it's our job to figure
out which one of you
bitches is the imposter
or we're all gonna die.
Are you serious, Psycho?
I know you heard me, you dumb bitch.
And if I recall correctly?
Didn't the Chaka who blew up say
something about not knowing who you were?
You two, can you back that up?
Do you remember seeing her when
we formed this search party?
You're one to talk!
We don't remember who you are either! Yo!
You do know that I was with y
'all from the jump, don't ya?
Sorry to say this, but I
can't say that I remember you.
Shut it!
Nobody knows who your scrawny
ass is either! Yes you do!
I'm the one who just called
for help on the radio!
Maybe you only did that to trick us!
Wait a minute.
You there with the black hair.
Why did your nose just start bleeding?
What the...?
I couldn't see all that well, but Ermes,
when I punched the enemy's stand in the
face, one of these three stumbled a bit.
Get back right now!
Stay away from the water!
No, you've got it all wrong!
My nose is bleeding because that bitch
hit me in the face when she grabbed me!
See, look!
Her bloody hand!
It's proof that she did it!
Are you for real?
I didn't hit her, my finger
just scraped her teeth!
I was most definitely here from
the start if anyone's the killer.
It's gotta be one of you.
Oh, yeah Remember what happened when
the chief was chatting with his Cutter?
You were over there talking mad shit
Ain't that right little miss bitch.
Yeah, that's true.
You know what the two of you
seem pretty suspicious, too
What
It's true, so the black hair did do it.
How the hell did you
figure out it was her?
Well, to tell the truth, I have
no idea if it actually was her.
That's why I'm just gonna
knock out all three of you!
You bitch!
Who the fuck do you think you are?
D-did she just...
Now my plan's ruined.
I wanted to kill you separately.
I was gonna get you into the
water and tear you to shreds.
But your little trick surprised me.
I really didn't think you could
get out of that situation,
but that threat power of
yours is a pain in the ass.
What the hell is going on with them?
It can't be all three of them, can it?
This doesn't make any sense.
Who's the actual stand user?
Once again, you're wrong.
Stand powers are special.
Each individual only gets one.
The girls who were actually
here from the very beginning
were the ones with the black
hair and the shaved head.
They decided to go near the tractors,
so I decided to kill them and take
over their bodies and intellect.
On the other hand, this body of mine is...
You need the body I
created from the scraps
of flesh left over from
the missing prisoners!
I have to hold my hand and hold my hand.
I'm going to turn around.
I'm going to trap and hate.
Okay, alright.
I'm a survival day.
Get away from.
No more time.
I don't wanna say it.
Let's go, go.
One, two, three.
Come and find a way.
Life for me.
I'm a my one.
That strange black goop is
coming out of their bodies.
My once divided body is now whole again.
If it is to protect the
power and memory that Pale
Snake's discs most
graciously bestowed upon me.
I am willing to do anything it takes
to repay the great debt I owe him.
It's my mission to get rid of anyone who
approaches the discs in the storehouse.
Damn it!
Where the fuck is the
actual stand user hiding?
Think again, Ermes.
The user is...
the thing itself! Huh?
It's alive.
See, this thing is a living
organism born in the water.
And from the discs, it gained power.
And the one guarding those discs
was never human to begin with.
A living organism?
Are you talking about all those
tiny killer plankton things?
Since the storehouse doesn't
have a constant supply of water,
it's probably moving by
consuming water from the
bodies of its victims in
order to protect the discs.
It exists on land by multiplying itself.
But there's a catch.
Just like gas for a car, it needs to
replenish its water when it runs out.
If we want to get the disks
back from this creature,
we have to make sure it doesn't get close
to the water, and then defeat it quickly.
Hold up, Jolene.
Even if all that crap is true, how can that
walking parasite with a face talk to us?
I am F .F.
You will call me by my name or not at all!
A famous astronomer by the
name of Fred Hoyle once said,
It is wrong to assume, even
probabilistically speaking,
that living organisms were
spontaneously born on this Earth.
The power of intellect was already a
pre-existing force in this universe,
and it is that intellect which
created the origin of life.
To put it another way, it can be said
intellect preceded even the Big Bang,
and that all organisms in matter itself
already possess that intellect. Huh?
What in the actual hell is it
going on about all of a sudden?
I think it seeks to prove
that human beings are
not the only ones capable
of having intellect.
Even planktons like it can make memories.
I said my name is FF!
Didn't you hear me?
It's painfully obvious I'm
more intelligent than you!
Not good.
It's going to hide the disks somewhere
new before we can get to them!
If it manages to bury them
underground, they'll be gone forever!
J-Jolene, there's something else.
Look behind us!
The one that attacked us in
the water earlier is back,
and it's trying to grab the guard.
Shit, the handcuffs!
If we get 50 meters away
from it, we're dead!
We're done, Jolene.
It's time to give up on the discs.
Our priority should be
protecting the guard's body?
Before we get blown up, because I'd
rather make it out of this in one piece.
You're right, but I'll let
you handle the handcuffs.
Hermes.
While I'm running to the storehouse,
it's up to you to protect the guard
and haul his body within my safety
range so my cop doesn't go off
and blow me up before I get there.
Got no choice.
Hey, hold on a second.
What a crazy bitch. That's ridiculous.
Why would she leave
something like that up to me?
But still, goddammit.
Once it pulls the guard's
body into the water,
both Jolene and I are going
to get blown to kingdom come.
I have no time to waste!
Hell yeah, I managed to do it.
But one thing's for sure,
after this bullshit, I ain't ever going
to use my stickers like this again.
I can't believe I actually had
to double my arm to do this.
Aw, man, I bet it's
gonna hurt like a bitch.
Now I just need to carry in within
50 meters of that stupid storehouse.
Water?
Damn you, you filthy little maggot!
That's a victory, Scream.
You think you've won, don't you, shithead?
Take a good look.
This is the corpse of that poor girl with
the undercut that your
other half sucked dry.
She's got no moisture left.
And now, thanks to my sticker,
she's been divided into two.
All I gotta do is pull it off.
That ought to absorb whatever
water is left over like a maxi pad.
Or should I say it'll dry up like
a drop of water in the desert.
Put a sock in it!
You're in my way!
Get lost, would ya?
Jolene, the only way we'll
win is if we dry it out.
In order to defeat that
disgusting parasite,
we've got to drain its tank
like it did those girls.
You actually made it.
I was going to kill you anyway.
You've just made it easier.
My original plan was to hide the discs
somewhere else and then
ask you some questions,
but no matter.
For now, answer me this.
Are you going to step into this puddle
I've made, or will you run for your life?
Which way would you like to die?
If we're asking questions,
I've got some too.
Do you know who the
one behind all this is?
Who exactly is Pale Snake?
Also, by gathering all the disks together,
what are they really hoping to achieve?
My, you're an interesting one.
I can understand the motive behind
fighting to protect yourself.
Or even fighting to protect your friends.
Well, that's not something I can relate
to, but I can see why you'd do it.
However, what I don't understand is why
you'd willingly walk in here to die.
Also, as for the one known as Pale Snake,
unfortunately, I don't know who they are.
Did you think I was
distracted, you moronic child?
The entirety of this puddle has
already become a part of my body!
Were you trying to soak
up the water with flour?
I commend your effort, but you failed.
Well, it was futile.
I have full understanding
of my power and created
an environment for myself
where I have no weaknesses.
Your body seems to be a worthy vessel.
Perhaps I can live inside of
it comfortably for a while.
Nah, because now you've already lost.
When you made this so-called
perfect environment for yourself,
you had to splatter
water all over the floor.
Wrong move.
While you were pondering
how to kill me you
didn't hear me start the
tractor with my threat.
I guess the sound of the
water masked the noise
so since you were
preoccupied i made my move.
The tractor has left the storehouse and
the discs you vowed to protect are gone.
You...
you asshole!
Remember what you have there!
Those discs are not yours to take!
Please stay with me!
Soil and Fields is a lot softer
than the area near the wetlands.
The more you run, the more water you lose.
And where you're going,
there ain't no water, either!
You vile care!
I'll never let you touch the disks!
Seems Jolene won this battle of wits.
Your precious disks no
longer belong to you.
This is it, asshole!
Dry up and spend the rest of your
days in this field as fertilizer!
Jolene?
Jolene, what do you think you're doing?!
I'm giving it water.
Basically, I'm saving it. Huh?
This being called FF.
It was never truly protecting the disks
because it's what Pale Snake wanted.
I can see that clearly now.
Even though it knew its body would slowly
diminish if it ran into the fields,
it continued chasing the tractor.
I think it was protecting the Discs as
a way of protecting its own identity.
Because of the power and intellect
given to it by the Discs,
it put its life on the line
out of gratitude for being
able to exist in this world
as an intelligent lifeform.
Essentially, it doesn't give a damn
about Pale Snake or what they want.
Wait, you're seriously helping it?
It murdered five people
without a second thought!
And in case you forgot, it
literally isn't even human! Exactly.
Think about what you just said.
If it's not human, it
probably isn't guilty either.
The one who's at fault here is Pale Snake.
That bastard only passed
along enough information
to allow them full control
over the situation.
Besides, that's not the only
reason that I want to help it out.
What do you say we make a deal?
Protect the Disks.
Continue to do what you've
been doing this entire time.
But instead, I want you to do it for us.
To protect them from Palesnake.
Let me be clear.
I have no intention of trying
to steal the Disks from you.
All I want is to get back the
Disks that were my father's.
Also, I want to know every
detail about Palesnake's agenda.
So how about it?
Will you help us out?
It's your choice, but there
will be no more killing.
Fuck me.
This is unbelievable.
Your strange sentiments.
I don't quite understand them very well,
but I don't feel like biting anymore.
And now, I've been defeated completely.
They really are here! We did it!
Alright, I finally found the
disc that contains Star Platinum!
Jolene!
Hey, are you okay?
Yeah, it rejected me, but it's
definitely Star Platinum's disc.
Now that I have this, I can
revive my father, Jotaro Kujo!
It's finally mine!
Yeah, bud.
For some reason I can't find the
one with his memories over here.
Did I miss it somehow?
Where could it be?
Hey, if I were to jump off from that
window up there, you think I'd die?
Hey, no need to get hostile, guys.
It's me! It's me!
Your new friend, FF!
I'd like to be called
that if you don't mind.
This body was the only usable one,
so I replaced her missing parts and snagged
this handcuff off one of the others.
I took a liking to how it feels, so I
decided to live in this body for a while.
Though it appears these fingers
aren't all that usable anymore.
Hold on, let me get this straight.
When you say live in her body,
does that mean you're planning to go
back to the prison pretending to be her?
Jolene, my new mission is to protect you.
And it's no big deal.
I have access to all of her memories.
She's Atro, and her
prisoner number is FV39423.
Back when she was just a little kid,
she always dreamed of being kidnapped.
So, when she grew up, she kidnapped
a child the way she wanted to be.
She didn't even do it for
ransom money or anything.
She sort of just did it.
Oh, hey, it looks like both
of your arms are bleeding.
So does it hurt?
I really wish I could
heal you, but I can't.
Get your tongue off of me, you grip!
What the hell are you doing?
Don't lick us!
It's water!
I hate you, water!
Yeah, you sure ain't human.
Before you go to prison, there
are some things you gotta learn.
I'd say drinking with a cup would
be a pretty good place to start.
A cup?
Why didn't you say so?
Oh, that's easy.
Drinking water out of a cup is nothing.
Alright, about what I said earlier, I
want to ask you more about Palesnake.
Do they make a habit of
coming out to this storehouse?
Nope.
They rarely have ever come near the tractor,
and I've never seen the user either.
The pile of discs here are the
ones that Palesnake doesn't need.
You probably know this already, but
no matter how strong a stand is,
if you don't have the constitution
for it, it'll reject you.
And that's why this is the junk pile.
To them, they're completely useless.
The important discs with all the
memories must be stored somewhere else.
That's why you won't be able to find
the memory disc you're looking for.
The thing pale snake wanted to
steal from your father wasn't his
ultimate stand but most likely it
was the memories inside his head.
I don't know what he has in there but
it's got to be a really important?
secret.
A secret?
The guards are here.
What's the plan, Jolene?
What are you gonna do with
Star Platinum's disc?
Well, before I can do anything
else, I've gotta figure out how to
get the disc out of this prison and to the
Foundation that's sheltering my father.
If
we don't revive him soon, his
body will begin to deteriorate.
Eventually,
I'll take back His memory
disc no matter what
it takes you want to get
it out of prison huh?
That's gonna be a lot harder
than if you were bringing
something in and when the guards
get here they're definitely
gonna inspect us from head
to toe get the disc to me all
I gotta do is bump my boobs
up a few coat sizes there!
FF, raise your hands in the air
so that they won't shoot you.
Ermes, same for you.
Our story is that an alligator
viciously attacked the guard,
and it was us who saved him.
Unfortunately, we don't know
about the other prisoners.
Just follow my lead, okay?
She played her role as Baitwell.
Jotaro's daughter was
only meant to lure him in.
I never thought she'd become
someone I'd need to worry about.
Jolene Kujo.
Is it possible she defeated that incompetent
guard and took the disc all by herself?
Or perhaps these other two
prisoners who survived were
there to lend Jolene a helping
hand in thwarting my plans.
Father, the sun will be setting soon.
We need to be getting
you back to the prison.
The chief has called off the search.
Are you really that worried about
prisoners that went missing, Father Pucci?
A while longer.
After all, I am on the overnight duty
until I must give the service on Sunday.
Although you think I cope,
my head is filled with hope.
Of some place other than here?
Although you think I smile,
Inside and all the while,
I'm wondering.
About my destiny?
I'm thinking about.
Out all the
things I'd
like to do in my life.
I'm a dreamer,
a distant dreamer,
dreaming for me.
From today
Thank you.
You